when there were fighting on the territory of the Donetsk Lugansk
когда на территории Донецкой Луганской
region until April 12, 1914,
области до 12 апреля четырнадцатого года
then look Andrey I’m
действия значит смотрите Андрей я
not a date blogger and not a number
не дата блогер и не цифра
blogger What an
блогер Какая
honor Andrey Popik himself And
честь сам Андрей Попик А вы
where are you from I’m from
откуда Я из
St. Petersburg I’m on the stream if anything
санкт-петербурга Я на стриме если что
How do you feel about the war
Как вы к войне
I  I have a bad attitude towards any war, the
относитесь я к любой войне отношусь
one that happened in Yugoslavia, and
плохо к той которая бола в Югославии и
so on and so on, I
так далее и так далее ко всем войнам
have a bad attitude towards all wars and who is to blame for the fact that
отношусь плохо а кто виноват в том что
Russia attacked
Россия напала на
Ukraine, I’ll repeat it again, I
Украину я ещё раз повторюсь я к войне
have a bad attitude towards war and what’s happening
отношусь плохо а то что происходит
now between Russia and Ukraine  - this is,
сейчас между Россией и Украиной - это к
unfortunately, a forced measure, as at one
сожалению вынужденная мера как в своё
time America called an
время вынужденная мера назвала Америка
attack on Iraq a forced measure, but look, it
нападение на Ирак да то смотрите
turns out that it’s the same and who forced who
получается Тай же ми а кто вынудил кто
forced Russia to attack
вынудил Россию напасть на
Ukraine. I won’t discuss with you who
Украину Я не буду с вами обсуждать кто
forced it because you still wo
это вынудил потому что вы мне всё равно
n’t believe me.  wait no Well, I’m interested in
не поверить подожди не Ну мне интересно
understanding your version, your
разобраться вот вашу версию ваше
worldview, I may disagree with it,
мировоззрение я могу с ним не
don’t believe you, I
согласиться не поверить вам У меня своё
may have my own opinion, but
может быть мнение новате обем
look, look, my
ния Смотри вот смотрите вот мо мо
worldview will somehow change the situation that is
мировоззрение как-то изменит ситуацию
happening now between
происходящую сейчас между
Ukraine. Why go out to the entrance?  you
Укра Зачем выходите в летку м вы
say, well, you know, very often
говорите ну знаете Очень часто
it turns out like this when people start
получается так когда люди начинают
sharing their worldview, it all
делиться своим мировоззрением это всё
develops into
перерастает в
rugos, you want to hear my
ругос хотите услышать моё
worldview, but I want you to hear it
мировоззрение но я вам отте услышать
peacefully,
мирово
when in what year did they start shouting at
то когда в чем году начинали кричать на
And don’t tell me that they didn’t
И не надо мне говорить что этого не
do this to the Gilyak, I understood  what are they
делали на гиляку я понимал что это
shouting? Specifically to me, Russian, Russian, we are
кричат Конкретно мне русского русский мы
you, and therefore I believe that the Russians
тебя и поэтому я считаю что русские
came to Ukraine to see where you have this
пришли на Украину посмотреть где у вас э
same Gelya. Wait, it was
та самая Геля Подождите на Украину
not Russians who came to Ukraine, but Russians, that is,
пришли не русские а россияне то есть
Chechens, Buryats, Russian Ukrainians who
чеченцы буряты русские украинцы которые
live in Russia, Russians
живут в России на Украину пришли русские
and Russians came to Ukraine.  It’s absolutely true, and it’s
а россияне Совершенно верно и против
not Ukrainians who are fighting against Russians,
россиян против россиян воюют не украинцы
but Ukrainians, Russian Jews, Poles, everyone Who
а украинцы русские евреи поляки все Кто
lives in Ukraine,
живёт в Украине
it’s true, Russians who live in Ukraine,
правда русские которые живут в Украине
Russians who live in Ukraine, so
русские которые живут в Украине так
residents of Kharkov, for example, Odessa,
жители Харькова так например Одессы там
Dnepropetrovsk, Yes, Dnieper. They are fighting
Днепропетровска Да Днепра Они воюют
against Russians now.
против россиян сейчас
True, including  there are Mercenaries so there are still
Правда в том числе есть Наёмники сль ещё
unwinding Russians Russians who live in
размот русски русские которые живут в
Kharkov in Odessa in the Dnieper There are
Харькове в Одессе в Днепре Там же есть
Russian
русские
people there too Yes of course they are
люди там же не токо Да есть конечно
certainly They are fighting now against
безусловно Они воюют сейчас против
Russia Yes there are Yes there are Russias yes that is
России Да есть Да есть России да то есть
it turns out Russians Russians various
получается россияне россияне разные
Russian Buryats Chechens and so on  then
русские буряты чеченцы и так дальше
they came and now
пришли и сейчас против них воюют
Ukrainians and Russians from Ukraine are fighting against them, so
украинцы и русские из Украины так
you will agree with me that now
Вы же со мной согласитесь что сейчас
Ukrainians, Buryats and
против Украины воюют украинцы буряты и
everything else, and all nationalities and
все прочее и все национальности и татары
Ukrainian Tatars and Ukrainians are fighting against Ukraine,
украинские и украинцы украинские против
no wait, please don’t
воют нет подождите пожалуйста не
interrupt nya I don’t interrupt, I  you didn’t
перебивайте ня Я не перебивай я же ва не
interrupt, you agree with
перебивал согласны вы со
me. So I can simply oppose you
мной Вот я могу вам просто оппонировать
now against Ukraine, just as they are fighting against
сейчас против Украины точно также против
Russia as they are fighting against Russia, in the same way
России как против России воют точно
Ukrainians are fighting against
также украинские Украин
all other nations plus e Nani from
пере все остальные нации плюс е Нани со
all over the world Ukrainians Ukrainians are not fighting
всего мира украински украинцы не воюют
against
против
Ukraine against Russia they are fighting Ukraine It’s me
Украины против России воют Укра Это я
so howled
так выл
Ukraine, Ukrainians with citizenship,
Украин украинцы имеющие гражданство
wait, I’ll clarify, Ukrainians with Ukrainian
подожди я уточню украинцы имеющие
citizenship are fighting now
гражданство Украины воюют
all the Russians who are citizens
вс русские которые есть гражданами
of Russia in the Wait Can you,
России во Подожди вых Можете вы их
I agree, Can you
можете Я согласен Можете вы Меня
interrupt me, let me listen to you, I
перебили давайте я Вас выслушал я вас
listened to you Now don’t interrupt me,
выслушал Теперь вы меня не перебивайте
look, there is also there  Russians who are
смотрите есть также есть русские которые
Citizens of the Russian Federation they are now
Граждане Российской Федерации они сейчас
fighting against Russia There is
воюют против России Есть
[music]
[музыка]
this There is this I told
такое Есть такое Я же сказал
you, that is, we just realized
вам то есть мы только что с вами поняли
that this is not Russia, not Russian, that
что это не Россия не рус
there are Ukrainians who, yes, look,
что есть украинцы которые да да смотрите
there is a citizenship, let’s fix it, there is
есть гражда зафиксируем есть
Ukraine Yes, there are citizens  Ukrainians who
Украин Да есть граждане Украины которые
are fighting against Ukraine and there are citizens
воюют против Украины и есть граждане
of Russia who are fighting against Russia
России которые воюют против России
Yes, they have recorded this Yes, I
Да есть зафиксировали есть такое Да
agree va zafiro Now look,
согласен ва зафиро Теперь смотрите
it means you just admitted that it was not the
значит вы только что признали что это не
Russians who came to protect the Russians Yes, this is
русские пришли защитить русских Да это
Russia, so all the different peoples of Russia were
Россия так все разные народы России да
thrown here to fight against everyone  different
бросили сюда воевать против всех разных
peoples of Ukraine
народов Украины
Well, you think that yes, well, that is, I don’t
Ну считаете что да ну то есть я же не
think that the Chechens or Buryats came
думаю что чеченцы или буряты пришли
to defend for this, that means not against the Gilyaks.
защищать за так то значит не на гиляки
It was
Дело было
so, you know, the thing is that if you
так вы знаете дело в том то что если вы
think that only I thought so, then you
думаете что так думал только я то вы
are mistaken, you could  the Chechens
ошибаетесь так могли думать и чеченцы
could think the same way, and the Buryats too. Don’t
так могли думать и буряты У вас же не
interrupt me, I’ll finish. You don’t have
перебивайте я закончу У вас же нет
statistics, I told you. You told me my
статистики я вам сказал Вы сказали моё
personal opinion and now you’re trying to
личное мнение а теперь вы пытаетесь моё
convey my personal opinion to everything, do
личное мнение транспортировать на всё не
n’t do this, please. That is, I
надо этого делать пожалуйста То есть я
understand correctly that the Chechens  Let's say
правильно понимаю что чеченцы Давай М
that the Chechens, having heard that in Kiev someone
что чеченцы услышав что в Киеве кто-то
said something in
сказал на
Gilyak, decided to defend and attacked
гиляку решили защитить и напали на
Ukraine.
Украину
Well, you know, I think that the world is so
Да ну знаете я думаю что мир настолько
wide and diverse that there could be a
широк разнообразен что там может быть
million options, one option is
миллион вариантов один вариант
really some Chechen,
действительно какой-нибудь чеченец вонял
it stank like a personal insult to oneself
это как как личное оскорбление себя
another Chechen could, let’s say, a Chechen, my
другой чеченец мог допустим чеченец мой
friend, relatively speaking, my friend saw how
друг условно говоря мой друг увидел как
it insulted me and went to defend
меня это Оскорбляет и пошёл защищать
me. The third person went because everyone went.
меня Третий ц пошёл потому что все пошли
Well, you know, the world is wide, you can’t
Ну вы знаете мир же он широк нельзя
say that all Chechens are the same and
сказать что все чеченцы они одинаковые и
they go. The incentive is the same  no
идут у них Стимул один и тот же нет У
Everyone is different, but I think that some of the
всех разные но думаю что кто-то из
Chechens could perceive this as
чеченцев мог воспринять это как
laziness, correctly
ление правильно
understanding Rita Tatars Bashkor came to
понима Риты татары башкор пришли в
Ukraine to protect
Украину защитить
Russians no Chechens Buryats Tashki Bashkirs
Русских нет чечены буряты Ташки башкиры
and so on they came to protect not
и так далее они пришли Защищать не
Russians they came to defend Russia this is the
русских они пришли защищать Россию это
Key important thing
Ключевое важно
of the foundation right yes  that
фундамента правильно да то
is, they are defending Russia and not some
есть они защищают Россию а не каких-то
Russians in Ukraine, and why did you
русских в Украине да то причём вы
say that Russia attacked Ukraine?
сказали что Россия напала на Украину
Because here you were shouting at the Gilyak, somehow
Потому что тут кричали на гиляку
you all lumped together, I did
вы как-то всё в одну в кучу я ни слова
n’t say a word about the fact that someone came
не сказал о том что кто-то пришёл
defend Russians Ukraine I said about
защищать русских Украину Я сказал про
my personal opinion that here are the programs you are
своё личное мнение что вот проги вы
now trying to lead me to how in
сейчас пытаетесь вести меня к тому как в
general there is no need Andrey Now let's wait
общее не надо Андрей Вот давайте подожди
Give me peace of mind I'm watching you sometimes I
Дайте спокой я наблюдаю за вашине иногда
like your streams I want to let you know
нравится ваши стримы Я хочу разб не надо
I just don't need to divide the conversation into parts
меня толь надо делить разговор на части
you have a cloud This is
у вас обло Вот это
with I want to understand You said that on
с Я я хочу понять Вот вы сказали что на
the Maidan they shouted at the Gilyak from this
Майдане кричали на гиляку из этого вот
That on the Maidan, for example, someone
Что вот на Майдане например кто-то
shouted at the Gilyak Yes, for example, even
крикнул на гиляк Да например даже
Poroshenko would say that What, for example,
Порошенко бы сказал бы что Что например
I don’t know or Poroshenko where is this  he
я не знаю или Порошенко где такое он
said yes, but let’s say he said that it is
говорил да но вот допустим он сказал что
necessary to attack Ukraine, so
надо чтобы напасть на Украину вот
explain why you are attacking
объяснить ну из-за чего вы нападает на
Ukraine, if in Sweden someone says against the
Украину если в Швеции кто-то скажет на
Gilyak, you are attacking Sweden,
гиляку вы напад на швецию
look, you don’t try to deduce
вот смотрите Вы не пытайтесь вывести
deduce these are my simple answers  to
вывести вот такие простые мои ответы на
globality You started with that And I
глобальность Вы же начали с того И я вас
remind you of this and started talking
вам об этом напоминаю и начали говорить
Why do you go to Roulette And I told
А зачем вы в Рулетку заходите А я сказал
you that you don’t seem to really find out anything here
вам что вы ничего здесь как бы не
All of us,
выясните по-настоящему Все мы с вами в
including you, are sitting and chatting a little
том числе и вы сидим немножко поболтать
so I told you Give me your
так вот я вам вы сказали Дайте мне своё
personal opinion I gave it to you Now you
личное мнение Я вам его дал Теперь вы
want to unwind my personal opinion throughout
моё личное мнение хотите разматывать по
this whole huge pie and
этому всему огромному пирогу и сделать
pretend that it’s a fact Everyone
вид что как будто это по факту Все так
thinks so Look, I’m not completely sure,
думают Смотри я не до конца
just let me clarify once again  or did I
просто е раз давайте я уточню или я
understand your opinion correctly, you said, I
правильно понял ваше мнение вы сказали я
understood that Russia attacked Ukraine
так понял что Россия напала на Украину
Because they were shouting here, did I understand correctly
Потому что тут кричали правильно я понял
or
или
not? I told you that if it’s just that in
нет Я вам сказал что если просто на
fact the question is very complex, very
самом деле вопрос очень сложный очень
complex and, as it were, extremely difficult, in
сложный и как бы крайне сложно вот в
such a conversation it is obligatory  How and why I am
таком разговоре обя что Как и почему я
exaggerating this because in fact, not
утрирование потому что на самом деле не
only Naga there was a lot of things there,
только Наги там было много чего
you know a lot of things. Well, now we are
понимаете много чего Ну мы сейчас тогда
just growing, everything is roaring, you understand everything
просто растём всё по реву понимаете всё
will be very complicated. I can’t understand what
будет очень слож Я не могу понять что
happened that you really need to
случилось такого что действительно надо
come to another country and  kill bomb
прийти в другую страну и убивать бомбить
in short there are hundreds of thousands of people so that
короче там сотни тысяч людей чтобы
millions run away from their homes tens of
миллионы убежали со своих домов десятки
hundreds of thousands died Yes, that is, I didn’t
сотни тысяч погибли Да ну то есть я не
say anything, explain ska now you
что говорили обясните ска тепер вы
are saying that you can tell me this
говорите что это вы утри можете мне назо
well I agree with you I yes I agree with you
хорошо Я с вами согласен я да я с вами
look in general  when some people
согласен смотрите вообще когда Одни люди
kill others it’s generally difficult to understand
убивают других это вообще трудно понять
it’s completely out of my head Here
это вообще в голове не укладывается Тут
I completely agree with you absolutely
я с вами полностью согласен абсолютно
completely agree But I don’t like the fact
полностью согласен Но мне не нравится то
that the Ukrainian Rona is very and you are in a
что украинская Рона очень и вы в том
very
очень
narrow period of time and don’t
узкий отрезок времени и как бы не
take it into account, that is, you know  there is a
учитывайте то есть знаете вот есть
reason for the investigative connection, you understand
причина следственной связи вам понятно
this, well, the phrase means the meaning of the phrase, the reason for the
это ну фраза смысл фразы причина
investigative connection, that is, you see,
следственно связи то есть Понимаете вот
not only was there a lot of things and people
было не только было много чего и людей
were killed. I think I absolutely believe in this,
убивали Я считаю я абсолютно в этому
don’t interrupt, starting in the
верю начи не перебивайте начиная с
fourteenth year in the fourteenth year, the
четырнадцатого года в четырнадцатом году
Civil War began in you
у вас началась Гражданская война
like  you don’t like it when you
нравится вам это не нравится когда у вас
had a
случился
private conversation I’ll finish and then support well I
привате я закончу а потом опору хорошо
’ll finish then they please you’re a smart
Закончу потом они пожалуйста вы умный
person you Please be patient
человек вы Потерпите
when Mr. Turchinov,
пожалуйста когда господин турчинов
being the acting
будучи исполняющим обязанности
president, sent troops And this was before
президента послал войска А это было до
Strelkov there, all this is known
Стрелкова там пода тамм всё это известно
and you know it very well  before
и вы это прекрасно знаете до
Strelkov, he sent troops to Donbass and
Стрелкова он послал войска в Донбасс а
Donbass was indignant at the fact that they overthrew there,
Донбасс возмутился тем что там свергли
no matter how it was a revolution or even just
неважно как революция или ещё как просто
overthrew Yanukovych, they said guys, we
свергли Януковича они сказали ребята нам
don’t like the new government. Let’s
новая власть не нравится Давайте
negotiate and instead of sitting down
договариваться и вместо того чтобы сесть
at the negotiating table and somehow coming to an agreement with them,
за стол переговоров и как-то с ними
come to an agreement and  then it would be that
договориться договориться и тогда бы
what is happening now, nothing would
этого то что сейчас происходит ничего бы
be those but the ranks, relatively
не было те но чинов условно
speaking So look, I immediately say there
говоря Значит смотрите Сразу говорю там
that you are Balabol one way or another, or you are mistaken,
что вы Балабол так или ошибаетесь
I explain why, which means neither the Donetsk
объясняю почему значит ни Донецкий
Regional Council nor the Lugansk Regional
областной Совет ни Луганский областной
Council spoke or accepted any statements
Совет Не выступал и не принимал никакие
about independence And so on, yes  that is,
о независимости И так дальше да то есть
local authorities who were elected by
власти местные которые были выбраны
all citizens of the Donetsk or Lugansk
всеми гражданами Донецкой или Луганской
regions Yes, they functioned normally and
областей Да нормально функционировали и
had no complaints against Kiev. So
Никаких претензий к Киеву не имели Так
you can look at this. If there is any
это можете посмотреть Если есть какое-то
decision of the Donetsk and Lugansk council
решение донецко и Луганского совета
Show me If you say Turchinov
Покажите Если вы говорите турчинов
sent troops to Donbass and before Strelkov
послал войска на Донбасс да до Стрелкова
Tell me  until April 12, when Strelkov
Скажите до 12 апреля когда стрелков
entered Slavyansk, when hostilities began,
зашёл в Славянске когда начались боевые
at least one military operation on the
действия хоть одни боевые действия на
territory of the Donetsk or Lugansk
территории Донецкой или Луганской
region, and I now admit, tell me,
области и я сейчас признаю Вот скажите
9 years ago, you should have already known this,
за 9 лет вы уже должны были это знать
when on the territory of the Donetsk Lugansk
когда на территории Донецкой Луганской
region, before
области до
means look Andre, I’m not the date  a blogger and
значит смотрите Андре я не дата блогер и
not a digital blogger and I have at hand,
не цифра блогер и у меня под рукой в
unlike you, none I like your
отличие от вас никаких Мне нравится ваша
smile but wait, wait I
улыбка но подождите подождите Я вас
respect you as a Ukrainian blogger I
уважаю как украинского такого блогера Я
respect you but
вас уважаю но
look I won’t really bring it up
смотрите действительно поднимать не буду
because they don’t sit in my head
потому что в голове они у меня не сидят
but I definitely  I can say
но я точно могу сказать
that Mr. Turchynov somewhere there
что господин турчинов где-то там вашей
declared to your Verkhovna Rada that we are starting
Верховной Раде заявил что мы начинаем
blah blah blah there because
ато бла-бла-бла там потому что люди
peaceful people took up arms. I don’t
мирные взяли об оружие в руки Я плохо
know the Ukrainian language well, but nevertheless it
знаю украинский язык но тем не менее это
was like that, I think it was on the seventh
было так это было по-моему седьмого
numbers
числа
[music]
[музыка]
let's do it like this, you said that you do
на давайте сделаем так вы сказали что вы
n't know you don't have it, let's do it like this, how old are you?
не знаете у вас нет давайте мы сделаем
You're a very
таким сколько вам дней Вот вы очень
interesting interlocutor, let's tell you how many days
интересный собеседник давайте вы скажите
you need to find these
сколько вам нужно дней чтобы найти эти
dates, and for example, we can
даты так и мы например сможем
talk on the phone without using roulette.  for example, I
созвониться не в рулетке Вот например я
’ll send you a telegram link to Google
скину вам в телеграме ссылку на Google
me there or to Zoom So we
me там или на Zoom Так мы вот так
’ll meet like this and have a really normal
встретимся и действительно нормально
conversation, you’ll show me, look,
поговорим вы мне покажете вот смотри
this is the date before April 12 there were military
такая дата до 12 апреля были боевые
operations there and there and there how long do you
действия там-то И там-то сколько вам
need week month day Well  look
нужно неделю месяц день Ну смотрите
Andrey, I’m now I’m now I’m
Андрей я сейчас нахожусь я сейчас я
now look, I’m now at the
сейчас смотрите я сейчас нахожусь на
dacha, it’s probably time for the next four
даче вот ближайшие четыре мне наверное
Well, it’s not like I won’t
время Ну не то что мне я не буду этим
do this. You see, yes, I’m resting, that’s
заниматься Я понимаете да я отдыхаю это
normal, although in principle, stop, I’m not
нормально хотя в принципе стоп п я не
refusing. Wait, well, if  you
отказываюсь Подождите ну вот если вы мне
will send me a phone number so I can contact you, I would be
скинете телефон для связи я бы с вами с
happy to talk to you. That’s for sure
удовольствием пообщался Это точно потому
because look now we are a little
что смотрите сейчас немножечко
distracted from our conversation,
отвлекаемся от нашего разговора
wait, let me because soon
подожди давайте я потому что скоро у
I will be running out of time.
меня уже время будет заканчиваться
Look, let’s mean How to find me, that
Смотри Давайте значит Как найти меня то
is, when you decide in a week
есть когда вы вот решите через неделю
or two What are you ready, yes, for example, well,
или две Что вы готовы да например вот ну
you have some facts so
вы имеете какие-то фак
that we can talk about the facts,
чтоб мы могли поговорить по фактам
go to any of my videos, I
заходите на любое моё видео у меня там
have a link to the Telegram channel and in the
есть ссылка на Telegram канал так и в
teleg channel there is a bot on how to write to me, yes,
teleg канале есть бот как мне писать да
that is, just write with  telegram and
то есть просто пишите с телеграма и всё
we all get in touch, we’ll agree, for example,
мы связываемся договоримся например
when to go on air. So I’ll send you
когда выйти в эфир Так я вам скину
a link, for example, or you tell me how many of you are there right
например ссылку или вы мне с сколько вас
now. Now he’s looking at
сейчас человек Сейчас смотрит на
Vass
васс
4271, already
4271 уже
look. Let’s all finish
вот смотрите Давайте Всё закончили
the conversation, disputes, I mean. Yes, in general,
разговор споры имеется в виду Да вообще
I like you as a Ukrainian blogger.  I
вы мне нравитесь как блогер украинский
always wanted to meet you,
мне всегда хотелось с вами встретиться
but on the contrary, I always expected that according to
но мне наоборот всегда ожидал что по
the facts,
фактам
yes, yes, but unfortunately it turned out that
да да но к сожалению получилось так что
I met you at the dacha. Being on a
я с вами встретился на даче Находясь у
weak computer, I have nothing. I’m
меня слабый компьютер у меня ничего нету
using my laptop as a
Я с ноутбука выступаю у меня телефон как
distribution. Well, everything seems to be very  it’s difficult I’m not
раздача Ну как бы всё очень сложно Я не
from home My channel is called
из дома Вот у меня канал называется
born in the USSR I never quarrel with anyone
рождён в ССР я как бы никогда ни с кем
and you see Yes, let’s uh-huh If you
не ругаюсь и вы же видите Да давайте угу
want, I’ll send it to you, look, it
А хотите я вам скину вот смотрите это
’ll be fine if I send you the link
будет нормально если я вам ссылку скину
I’d like yours  guys
Я бы хотел бы чтобы Ваши ребята ко мне
would subscribe to me I need subscribers
бы подписались Мне нужны абоненты
who would like to watch my video so why Well,
которые бы на моё видео чтоб Зачем Ну
ours won’t subscribe to you why
наши не будут к вам подписываться зачем
like watch Everything I understand your channel I understand
типа смотрите Всё я ваш канал понял я
you and I would like this watch we’ll
вас а я бы этого хотел смотрите мы
do it means we’ll write off So you’ll come
сделаем значит спишемся Так вы приедете
from the dacha you’ll have  For example, you
с дачи у вас будет время вы например
will prepare time so that we can do more Because there is a
подготовите чтобы мы более Потому что
lot of chat roulette here. I really
тут очень много в чат рулетки Я очень
like thematic conversations on
люблю вот тематические разговоры по
facts. We can all talk. If you
фактам Всё мы можем поговорить Если вы
claim that Turchynov sent
утверждаете что у нас турчинов послал
troops to the Donbass, look at how
войска на Донбасс смотрите А как это
simple it is, you will understand me in this area
просто вы мне поймите я в этой сфере
Look, I’ve been in this area for only 2 months,
Смотрите я в этой сфере всего 2 месяца
only 2 months, 2 months, no, I
всего 2 месяца 2 месяца всего нет я в
mean, I went to Roulette more often, of course, but I
смысле в Рулетку заходил чаще безусловно
started going on air, see How
а стал в эфиры выходить смотрите Как как
can I call you, I just don’t understand
созвониться можно я просто не понимаю
how this will happen Yes, look, for
как это будет происходить Да смотрите
example, you have a program there
например вот у вас есть там программа
or Google Meet or Zoom for example or
или Google Meet или Zoom например или
Skype, whatever is convenient for us Yes,
Skype любое которое будет нам удобно Да
for example, a link is made there and I will
например там делается ссылка и я вам
send it to you using this link and connect
скидають по этой ссылке и подсоединяется
to the call and we will do the same as in two
к звонку и мы вот так же как в двух
screens, that is, we will try before the broadcast
экранчик будем то есть мы перед эфиром
for you to set up how it is
попробуем чтобы вы настроили как оно
to stream like this, for example, that’s all, and
чтобы стрими так например вот и всё и
then on the stream. Can I do this
потом на стриме Можно я вот так делал
already with some of the guys?
уже с ребятами некоторыми бы с вами я бы
Oh, by the way, let’s say this is
я очень часто О кстати вот давайте это
very important, I remember you very, very
очень важно я помню вы очень так очень
rudely bullied one unprepared
грубо загнобили одного неподготовленного
boy and you talked about the fact that he
мальчика и вы разговаривали о том что он
was from the DPR and you started
был из ДНР и вы там начали у него
asking him What do you call a village
спрашивать А как вы называете деревне
or something like that? Do you remember such a
или что-то вроде этого Помните такой
conversation?  I remember I could troll and
разговор не помн я мо троллить мог и
that you were trolling, if you had run
что вы троллили вот если бы вы нарвались
into me, I would have clearly put you in your
на меня я бы вас чётко поставил бы на
place, but this trolling is not good.
место вот с этим троллингом не хорошо е
Okay, but I just felt bad for
ли Ладно но мне просто стало обидно за
this boy. Well, that is, look,
этого мальчика Ну то есть смотрите
let’s not let you  Yes no no no well
давайте так чтоб вы не Да нет нет нет ну
when this boy from the DPR he didn’t No
когда вот этот мальчик из ДНР он не Не
well he couldn’t answer how well because
ну он не смог ответить как ну потому что
you know if by your logic then in Germany
понимаете если по вашей логике то в ФРГ
they live in Germany in a vat no so look at me
они живут в ФРГ в чане нет так смотри я
or there and so on you understand the DPRK is
или там ну и так далее понимаете КНДР
blood  I could troll someone Yes I
кровне я мог кого-то и троллить Да я
sometimes tro Well it was yours it didn’t matter all of this
иног тро Ну это ваш был неважно всё это
was forgotten by you Just every day there are
был забыли у вас Просто каждый день
a lot of conversations I if there is a person with
много разговоров я если есть человек с
whom you can talk seriously I
которым можно говорить по серьёзному Я
talk seriously No problem Here you and I
говорю по-серьёзному Без проблем Вот мы
are talking now  We don’t swear, we
с вами сейчас говорим мы же не ругаемся
really don’t call names, everything is super, yes, you’re
правда не обзываем всё супер да вы
looking, Let’s tell me please, here’s
смотрите Давайте хорошо скажите
yours Well, say in
пожалуйста вот ваше вашем Ну говорите в
your human definition I’m in what
вашем человеко определении Я в какой
category now I mean in
категории сейчас нахожусь в смысле в
my human definition
моём человеко определении
Well, I’m a smart person, I Well, I don’t know how it’s
Ну я умный человек я Ну не знаю как
interesting to
котом интересно
communicate with a cat if  I’m telling you that Let’s
общаться если я вам говорю что Давайте
meet, it means I’m interested in you, yes, that is, it’s
встре значит вы мне интересно да то есть
interesting with you because in chat
с вами интересно потому что в чат
roulette the majority of people shout this
рулетке большинство это такое там кричит
and so on with you we can
И так дальше с вами можно
argue, we can For example, I
аргументировано мы можем Например я
listened to you, I like this format
послушал вас мне такой формат нравится
and the audience also likes it because
да и зрителям это также нравится потому
that people want not just shouting, but a
что люди хотят не просто крики а
substantive conversation, this is interesting to everyone, you
предметный разговор это интересно всем
understand, that is, to get to the bottom
понимаете то есть вот докопаться до
of the truth Yes, and I always I to all Russians You
истины Да и я всегда я всем россиянам
can Who says to write to me and
Вот можете Кто там говорит писать мне и
we’ll call and we’ll do something like
мы созвонимся и мы сделаем такие типа
a battle on these issues I’m always ready
Батл вот по этих вопросах Я всегда готов
I  I agree it will be interesting, look
я согласен это будет интересно смотрите
Well, it will probably be like this, look, I will
Ну наверное будет это так смотрите я
really contact you and most
действительно с вами свяжусь и скорее
likely I remind you that I have only
всего я Напоминаю что я всего 2 месяца в
been in this field for 2 months, I am of course not as
этой сфере сижу я конечно не такой
pumped up as you and probably our
прокаченный как вы и наверное наш
conversation with you will probably be there in two in
разговор с вами возможно будет там два в
three stages  That is, you give me something there, I ca
три этапа То есть вы мне там что-то
n’t cope with something,
накидайте я с чем-то не справлюсь
relatively speaking, I’ll say Give me a
условно говоря скажу Дайте мне там ещё
couple more days there, it’s very easy there, I’m
пару дней я там очень просто вот я
already going now, give me a couple more, you
сейчас уже гою дайте мне ещ пару вы
Find This is the time when you
Найдите Вот за это там время когда вы
arrive from the dacha  Find out what kind of military
приедете с дачи Найдите Какие боевые
operations there were in the Donbass until April 12 of
действия были на Донбассе до 12 апреля
what year until the arrow came and now you
чего года пока пришёл стрелку и вот вы
show it to me, damn it, there were all
мне это покажете я блин ну всё были
military operations, there are people killed here, they were bombed, it
боевые действия вот есть убитые тут
will be easy to give for
разбомбили это же будет просто дасть за
9 le Let’s
9 ле Давайте нам с
give us a simple one,
простого давам
this is the situation about  to whom they said that
вот та ситуация о которой говорили это у
their air conditioner
них кондиционер
exploded e time for me in Wait for me
взорвался е раз мне через Подождите мне
in 3 minutes I need to switch off So
через 3 минуты Надо отключаться Так
let’s get you ready, so we
давайте вы подготовите так вот мы
agreed So let’s get together about
договорились Так и соберёмся про
the air conditioner it was already the month of June it was
кондиционер это уже был июнь месяц это
already a war in full swing Yes, we’ll
уже война полным ходом шла Да мы сначала
sort it out first You said that  Turchi
разберём Вы же сказали что турчи
sent a veska to the Donbass, we'll
отправил веска на Донбасс мы с этим
sort this out and then we'll move on to other
разберёмся и дальше пойдём по другим
things, that's all I'm just going to have to
каким-то этим всё Я просто уже должен
finish
сейчас финишировать
everything now Andrey, I'm listening, I'm happy I'm happy
всё Андрей я я слушайте Я доволен Я
that I ran into you, this is the first
доволен что я на вас нарвался это первое
I'm happy that I'm with you Okay, calm
Я доволен что я с вами Хорошо спокойно
talked about this two I'm glad that you
поговорил это два Я доволен что вы мне
gave me some kind of link to yourself, damn it, damn it, you
дали какую-то ссылку на себя блин блин
turned it off and turned it on
отключил его ви включил
So keep it up Sai Roulette on the
Так всё бачите вже Сай Рулетка на
grill C new channel Write to Nyogo right
грила Ц новый канал Пиши на нього прямо
away Putting the dialer to turn off the SPO forever
зараз Постав дзвоник щоб отримати ус СПО
we'll be on the
вчення будем на
link L
звязку L